+421 919 395 625 +420 725 250 010 Filip.karika1@gmail.com Fodorová 768 Slovakia, Važec 032 61

Filip Karika

Hello, my name is Filip Karika, and I am 21 years old. I am a junior in the field of computer science, and my greatest passion is programming. Ever since I was a child, I dreamed that one day my programs would make the world a better place. That's why, after high school, I decided to stay in the field and continue improving. I am currently a second-year student at Unicorn University in Prague, enrolled in the Software Development program. Since I have been involved in the IT world since I was 15, I am ready to apply my knowledge and dedication to professional IT development.

SKILLS

EXPERT

- Python
- JavaScript
- React JS
- Node JS
- Express JS
- MongoDB
- HTML
- CSS
- English (B2-C1)

ADVANCED

- Linux OS
- Algorithms
- Data structures
- SOL
- MICROSOFT OFFICE
- Git
- Github

BEGINNER

- Photoshop Illustrator
- UX/UI
- Arduino Cisco - CCNA
- C++

Personal website - https://sknefi.github.io/

Github -https://github.com/sknefi

LinkedIn - https://sk.linkedin.com/in/filip-karika-13b5072b0

EDUCATION

Súkromná stredná odborná škola Ul. 29. augusta 4812 Poprad, Informatics 2018 - 2022

2022 - 2023 Univerzita Karlova, matematicko-fyzikálna fakulta, Informatics

Unicorn Vysoká škola s. r. o., Software developmnet 2023 - present

2024 - present 42 Prague, Software Engineering

EXPERIENCE

07/2022 - 08/2022

CNC machine operator: Stolárstvo u Kunaja, s.r.o.

- Summer part-time
- Assisted in CNC machine operation, we were processing doors and windows from unprocessed wood.

07/2023 - 08/2023

Lifeguard: Hotel Permon 4*, Hotel Pieris 3*

- Summer part-time
- Taking care of the guests, swimming pool, tobogans, and other facilities. Helping injured guests and guests with disabilities.

09/2022 - present

Bartender: Frýdecko-Místecká Tančírna

- Once in a 1-2 months
- Pomoc s prípravou, miešanie drinkov, komunikácia so zákazníkmi

08/2024 - present

Lector: Lionscz

- Part-time, remote
- Creating manuals for students (Python, JavaScript)
- Create subject, write code, document code, explain code into Word + graphic editing in Word